<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<GameData>
	<EnglishText>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CONCEPTS_PAGEGROUP_EPSTWEAK_ADAPTATION_GROUP_NAME"><Text>Adaptation</Text></Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CONCEPTS_PAGE_EPSTWEAK_ADAPTATION_CHAPTER_EPSTWEAK_ADAPT_TITLE"><Text>Adaptation</Text></Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CONCEPTS_PAGE_EPSTWEAK_ADAPTATION_CHAPTER_EPSTWEAK_ADAPT_PARA_1"><Text>When you settle your original capital, the game checks the surrounding terrain within a 2-tile radius. If it detects a high number of tundra, desert, or mountain tiles, it gives your empire a special bonus to help cope with that type of environment. This bonus is permanent - it lasts until the end of the game, and applies to all of your cities.</Text></Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CONCEPTS_PAGE_EPSTWEAK_ADAPTATION_CHAPTER_EPSTWEAK_ADAPT_PARA_2"><Text>There are a few things to keep in mind:[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]It does not matter whether the surrounding tiles are owned by you or not.[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Only your capital can give you an adaptation bonus. Subsequent settled cities do not.[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]It is possible (though extremely rare) to get two adaptations at once.[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Tundra Mountains and Desert Mountains count towards the mountain adaptation, NOT the tundra or desert adaptations.[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Some civilizations have special exceptions where they will only get part of an adaptation bonus, or none at all. Those are listed below next to each possible adaptation.</Text></Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CONCEPTS_PAGE_EPSTWEAK_ADAPTATION_CHAPTER_EPSTWEAK_TUNDRA_TITLE"><Text>Tundra adaptation</Text></Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CONCEPTS_PAGE_EPSTWEAK_ADAPTATION_CHAPTER_EPSTWEAK_TUNDRA_PARA_1"><Text>If there are 7 or more Tundra/Tundra Hills or Snow/Snow Hills tiles within 2 tiles of your capital when it's founded, your civilization will adapt to life in the tundra.</Text></Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CONCEPTS_PAGE_EPSTWEAK_ADAPTATION_CHAPTER_EPSTWEAK_TUNDRA_PARA_2"><Text>Getting this adaptation grants your Builders the ability to build Farms on flat Tundra tiles straight away, as well as on Tundra Hills at Civil Engineering. And any Farms that you do build on tundra will get +1 [ICON_Production] Production.</Text></Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CONCEPTS_PAGE_EPSTWEAK_ADAPTATION_CHAPTER_EPSTWEAK_TUNDRA_PARA_3"><Text>Exceptions:[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Russia will not get extra [ICON_Production] Production on its tundra Farms.[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Canada will not get any bonus from this adaptation.</Text></Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CONCEPTS_PAGE_EPSTWEAK_ADAPTATION_CHAPTER_EPSTWEAK_DESERT_TITLE"><Text>Desert adaptation</Text></Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CONCEPTS_PAGE_EPSTWEAK_ADAPTATION_CHAPTER_EPSTWEAK_DESERT_PARA_1"><Text>If there are 7 or more Desert/Desert Hills tiles within 2 tiles of your capital when it's founded, your civilization will adapt to life in the desert.</Text></Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CONCEPTS_PAGE_EPSTWEAK_ADAPTATION_CHAPTER_EPSTWEAK_DESERT_PARA_2"><Text>Getting this adaptation grants your Builders the ability to build Farms on flat Desert tiles straight away, as well as on Desert Hills at Civil Engineering. And any Farms that you do build on desert will get +1 [ICON_Production] Production and [ICON_Faith] Faith.</Text></Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CONCEPTS_PAGE_EPSTWEAK_ADAPTATION_CHAPTER_EPSTWEAK_DESERT_PARA_3"><Text>Exceptions:[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Mali will not get extra [ICON_Faith] Faith on its desert Farms.</Text></Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CONCEPTS_PAGE_EPSTWEAK_ADAPTATION_CHAPTER_EPSTWEAK_MOUNTAINS_TITLE"><Text>Mountain adaptation</Text></Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CONCEPTS_PAGE_EPSTWEAK_ADAPTATION_CHAPTER_EPSTWEAK_MOUNTAINS_PARA_1"><Text>If there are 5 or more Mountain tiles within 2 tiles of your capital when it's founded, your civilization will adapt to life in the mountains.</Text></Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CONCEPTS_PAGE_EPSTWEAK_ADAPTATION_CHAPTER_EPSTWEAK_MOUNTAINS_PARA_2"><Text>Getting this adaptation grants your [ICON_Citizen] Citizens the ability to work mountain tiles, with a base yield of 1 [ICON_Production] Production and 1 [ICON_Faith] Faith. In addition to this, your mountains will gain +1 [ICON_Food] Food per adjacent Farm.</Text></Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CONCEPTS_PAGE_EPSTWEAK_ADAPTATION_CHAPTER_EPSTWEAK_MOUNTAINS_PARA_3"><Text>Exceptions:[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Inca's mountains will not gain extra [ICON_Production] Production, but they will gain +1 [ICON_Faith] Faith, and the extra [ICON_Food] Food from regular Farms in addition to Terrace Farms.</Text></Row>
	</EnglishText>
</GameData>
