<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Text -->
<!-- Author: Plati -->
<GameData>
	<BaseGameText>
		<!-- Core -->
		<Row tag="LOC_UNIT_GREAT_GreatSovereigns_NAME" >
			<Text>Great Sovereign</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_CLASS_GreatSovereigns_NAME" >
			<Text>Great Sovereign</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_PROJECT_GreatSovereigns_DISTRICT_GOVERNMENT_NAME" >
			<Text>Meritocratic Reforms</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_PROJECT_GreatSovereigns_DISTRICT_GOVERNMENT_DESCRIPTION" >
			<Text>Grants [ICON_GOLD] Gold equal to 15% of City [ICON_Production] Production output. Grants [ICON_GreatSovereigns] Great Sovereign points upon completion.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_UNIT_GREAT_GreatSovereigns_DESCRIPTION" >
			<Text>Great Sovereigns constitute of Rulers, not necessarily Monarchs, wielding major power over decision making and cast their shadow in History. Needless to say, many Sovereigns did Great deeds - often terrible and horrifying, but great indeed: caused wars, destroyed countries and led to deaths of millions. Those that are painted 'Great' happen to also be the ones that sparked the beginning of Golden Ages, created Great Wonders, made countries and people rise from obscurity and gain the status of Civilization worthy of Envy. Ages of Prosperity, immense feats or historical moments often owe gratitude to a sum of people, such as the 'Fathers' of United States or Italy. Great Sovereigns, however, are single individuals who changed history thanks to their shrewd statesmanship and apt rule. While some rulers certainly accomplished much, those that lost significant wars, lost their countries or lost millions of their own population don't really ring 'Great'.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- People -->
		<Row tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_FIRST_NAME" >
			<Text>Solomon</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREATPERSON_PLATI_FIRST_ACTIVE" >
			<Text>Instantly builds a Temple in this city. Temples provide +2 [ICON_Production] Production.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_PEDIA_GREATPEOPLE_PAGE_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_FIRST_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" >
			<Text>Solomon, also called Jedidiah, was monarch of ancient Israel and the son and successor of David, according to the Hebrew Bible and the Old Testament. He is described as having been the penultimate ruler of an amalgamated Israel and Judah. The hypothesized dates of Solomon's reign are from 970–931 BCE. The Bible says Solomon built the First Temple in Jerusalem, dedicating the temple to Yahweh, or God in Judaism. Solomon is portrayed as wealthy, wise and powerful, and as one of the 48 Jewish prophets. He is also the subject of many later references and legends, most notably in the Testament of Solomon (part of first-century biblical apocrypha). As with most biblical personages in the middle era of Israelite society, the historicity of Solomon is hotly debated. Current consensus states that regardless of whether or not a man named Solomon truly reigned as king over the Judean hills in the tenth century BCE, the Biblical descriptions of his apparent empire's lavishness is almost surely an anachronistic exaggeration. As for Solomon himself, scholars on both the maximalist and minimalist sides of the spectrum of biblical archeology generally agree that he probably existed. However, a historically accurate picture of the Davidic king is difficult to construct. According to some archaeologists, Solomon could have only been the monarch or chieftain of Judah, and that the northern kingdom was a separate development. Such positions have been criticized by other archaeologists and scholars, who argue that a united monarchy did exist in the 10th century BCE, while agreeing that the biblical account contains exaggerations.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_SECOND_NAME" >
			<Text>Marcus Aurelius</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREATPERSON_PLATI_SECOND_ACTIVE" >
			<Text>Grants [ICON_CivicBoosted] Boost to all Medieval Era Civics.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_PEDIA_GREATPEOPLE_PAGE_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_SECOND_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" >
			<Text>Marcus Aurelius Antoninus was Roman emperor from 161 to 180 AD and a Stoic philosopher. He was the last of the rulers known, noncontemporaneously, as the Five Good Emperors and the last emperor of the Pax Romana, an age of relative peace, calmness and stability for the Roman Empire lasting from 27 BC to 180 AD. Marcus acquired the reputation of a philosopher king within his lifetime, and the title would remain after his death; both Dio and the biographer call him "the philosopher". Christians such as Justin Martyr, Athenagoras, and Eusebius also gave him the title. The latter went so far as to call him "more philanthropic and philosophic" than Antoninus and Hadrian, and set him against the persecuting emperors Domitian and Nero to make the contrast bolder. The historian Herodian wrote: 'Alone of the emperors, he gave proof of his learning not by mere words or knowledge of philosophical doctrines but by his blameless character and temperate way of life.' </Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_THIRD_NAME" >
			<Text>Darius I</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREATPERSON_PLATI_THIRD_ACTIVE" >
			<Text>Grants 100 [ICON_Production] Production towards Wonder construction. Increases [ICON_TradeRoute] Trade Route capacity by 1.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_PEDIA_GREATPEOPLE_PAGE_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_THIRD_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" >
			<Text>The son of a satrap (governor) of Parthia, Darius I forcibly took the throne of Persia upon the death of Cambyses II in 522 BC. An administrative genius, during his reign Darius reorganized the sprawling Persian empire, greatly increasing its wealth and power. He also implemented many great construction works across Persia. When not battling one of his empire's neighbors, Darius took a series of actions to unify the empire and to improve its administration. He completed the organization of the empire into satrapies (provinces) and set the annual tribute due from each. He improved the Persian road network and standardized coinage, weights and measures, greatly expanding the opportunities for trade throughout the empire. He funded exploration expeditions from India to Egypt, and he completed a canal in Egypt leading from the Nile River to the Red Sea. Darius was the greatest builder in the Achaemenid Persian history. He constructed fortifications, a palace, and administrative buildings at Susa, his administrative capital. In his native Persepolis, Darius began construction of a new palace, as well as a council hall, treasury, and more fortifications (though these would not be completed until after his death). While firmly putting down any attempts at insurrection within Persia, Darius showed a good deal of tolerance to his subject peoples' religious beliefs. He constructed a number of temples in Egypt honoring the Egyptian gods, and he ordered his Egyptian satrap to codify the Egyptian laws in consultation with the Egyptian priestly class. In 519 he allowed the Jews to begin reconstruction of the Temple at Jerusalem. Darius himself is thought to have been a follower of Zoroastrianism, which was eventually made the state religion of Persia. History's view of Darius is generally quite favorable (if you put aside his questionable ascension to power, which was pretty much standard operating procedure throughout much of history). He constructed roads, reorganized the Persian provinces and government, secured the empire's borders, and generally treated his subjects about as well as or better than anyone in that time. Although not primarily known as a warlord, he fought a number of successful campaigns against both internal and external foes. It is quite possible that he could have successfully subjugated Greece if death had not intervened. His son, Xerxes I, certainly wasn't up to the task. All in all, Darius left his empire in better condition than he found it, which is a pretty good epitaph for any leader in any time period.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_FOURTH_NAME" >
			<Text>Asoka</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREATPERSON_PLATI_FOURTH_ACTIVE" >
			<Text>Cities recieve +1 [ICON_FAITH] Faith for each Specialty [ICON_DISTRICT] District.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_PEDIA_GREATPEOPLE_PAGE_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_FOURTH_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" >
			<Text>Asoka was one of the greatest rulers of ancient India. He brought nearly all of India (plus Afghanistan and Baluchistan) under one rule for the first (and thus far, only) time in history. Despite his great military prowess, Asoka grew weary of war and over time he became disgusted at its stupidity and pointlessness. A popular young general and statesman, Asoka ascended to the Mauryan throne upon his father's death in 273 BC, at the approximate age of 26. He began his rule as a conqueror, seeking to expand his nation's power across the Indian subcontinent and beyond. He was quite successful, and his empire grew. However, after his bloody conquest of the Kalinga state in which over 100,000 people died and another 150,000 were injured, Asoka underwent a great spiritual change. Deeply remorseful for all of the suffering he had caused, he abandoned wars of conquest and accepted Buddhism. He turned from expansion and instead concentrated upon improving the spiritual and physical well-being of his people. He modified many of his country's harsh laws, and he advocated tolerance of all faiths. He built many Buddhist monasteries throughout the land, and the arts flourished under his rule. He sent Buddhist missionaries across the known world, including to faraway places like Greece and Egypt. Despite his fervent belief in Buddhism, Asoka demanded religious tolerance in his kingdom, saying, "Beloved-of-the-Gods, King Asoka desires that all religions should reside everywhere, for all of them desire self-control and purity of heart." Asoka died in 232 BC, and the empire he built lasted only fifty years after his death. His name would be virtually lost to history now, if it weren't for the discovery of a large number of columns and boulders inscribed with his words and teachings. These "Edicts of Asoka" contain not only a fount of information about King Asoka, showing him as a wise and thoughtful ruler, but they also provide invaluable knowledge of the early teachings and beliefs of Buddhism.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_FIFTH_NAME" >
			<Text>Frederick II</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREATPERSON_PLATI_FIFTH_ACTIVE" >
			<Text>One free Economic Policy slot in any Government.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_PEDIA_GREATPEOPLE_PAGE_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_FIFTH_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" >
			<Text>Frederick II was King of Sicily from 1198, King of Germany from 1212, King of Italy and Holy Roman Emperor from 1220 and King of Jerusalem from 1225. His political and cultural ambitions were enormous as he ruled a vast area, beginning with Sicily and stretching through Italy all the way north to Germany. As the Crusades progressed, he acquired control of Jerusalem and styled himself its king. However, the Papacy became his enemy, and it eventually prevailed. Viewing himself as a direct successor to the Roman emperors of antiquity, he was Emperor of the Romans from his papal coronation in 1220 until his death; he was also a claimant to the title of King of the Romans from 1212 and unopposed holder of that monarchy from 1215. As such, he was King of Germany, of Italy, and of Burgundy. At the age of three, he was crowned King of Sicily as a co-ruler with his mother, Constance of Hauteville, the daughter of Roger II of Sicily. His other royal title was King of Jerusalem by virtue of marriage and his connection with the Sixth Crusade. Frequently at war with the papacy, which was hemmed in between Frederick's lands in northern Italy and his Kingdom of Sicily (the Regno) to the south, he was excommunicated three times and often vilified in pro-papal chronicles of the time and after. Pope Gregory IX went so far as to call him an Antichrist. Speaking six languages (Latin, Sicilian, Middle High German, French, Greek, and Arabic), Frederick has a reputation as a Renaissance man avant la lettre, as scientist, scholar, architect, poet and composer. As an avid patron of science and the arts, he played a major role in promoting literature through the Sicilian School of poetry. His Sicilian royal court in Palermo, beginning around 1220, saw the first use of a literary form of an Italo-Romance language, Sicilian. The poetry that emanated from the school had a significant influence on literature and on what was to become the modern Italian language. He was also the first king to formally outlaw trial by ordeal, which had come to be viewed as superstitious. A man of extraordinary culture, energy, and ability – called by a contemporary chronicler stupor mundi (the wonder of the world), by Nietzsche the first European, and by many historians the first modern ruler – Frederick established in Sicily and southern Italy something very much like a modern, centrally governed kingdom with an efficient bureaucracy.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_SIXTH_NAME" >
			<Text>Ahmad al-Mansur</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREATPERSON_PLATI_SIXTH_ACTIVE" >
			<Text>One free Diplomatic Policy slot in any Government.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_PEDIA_GREATPEOPLE_PAGE_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_SIXTH_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" >
			<Text>As one of the most influential leaders in the history of North Africa, Ahmad al-Mansur had a pivotal impact on the future of Morocco. Serving as the sixth Sultan of the Saadi Dynasty during the 16th century AD, Ahmad al-Mansur was known as a cunning diplomat who leveraged Morocco's strategic location to position his kingdom as a major player on the world's stage during the Renaissance. Ahmad al-Mansur is widely viewed today as one of history's greatest diplomats, excelling in the art of balancing friend and foe, Christian and Muslim. Al-Mansur's carefully crafted diplomatic schemes are credited with allowing Morocco's continued independence despite the scheming of many neighboring kingdoms as well as the powerful Ottoman Empire. His reign was marked by religious tolerance, scientific learning, and an artistic flowering in North Africa not known for many decades before or after.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_SEVENTH_NAME" >
			<Text>Charlemagne</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREATPERSON_PLATI_SEVENTH_ACTIVE" >
			<Text>One free Military Policy slot in any Government.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_PEDIA_GREATPEOPLE_PAGE_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_SEVENTH_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" >
			<Text>Charles the Great, Emperor of the Holy Roman Empire, fathered a kingdom that encompassed France, Germany, Italy and much of Eastern Europe. Legends of his conquests are pervasive throughout history, and he is considered one of the great figureheads of European Chivalric society. During his lifetime Charlemagne successfully campaigned in many countries. Some wars he completed personally and others were left for his sons to finish. His first campaign was against Desiderius of Lombardy who, soon after the succession of Pope Hadrian I, marched on Rome. Charlemagne pressed into Lombardy, and after a lengthy siege (772-774), he accepted Desiderius' unconditional surrender. Desiderius would live out the remainder of his life confined to a monastery. The longest lasting and most challenging conquest of Charlemagne's reign would be that of Saxonia. It would be a theater that he would continually revisit during his lifetime. After Charlemagne's initial push into Saxonia he was continuously forced to retake previously conquered land which had rebelled against his authority. Weary of war and losing more rights and freedoms with every capitulation, the Saxons eventually accepted Charlemagne's terms, including renouncement of their national religious customs and adoption of the Christian faith and its associated Frankish customs. Charles was both a highly religious man and a philanthropist. He often built friendly relationships with other countries, such as Egypt and India, so that he could later send money in an effort to assist struggling Christians in those regions. Although much more of a conqueror than an economic or social reformer, Charles often contributed money to relieve the poor and sick in his kingdom. Charlemagne, despite being unable to write well himself, had a vast love of literature and education. Due to his conquests, Charlemagne came into contact with many different cultures and learning institutions. Having contributed considerable funding to existing monastic schools and institutions of learning, Charlemagne's era became known as the Carolingian Renaissance, with a blossoming of the arts and sciences. As a member of the Nine Worthies, a group of both fictional and real people that represented the pinnacle of chivalry during their eras, Charlemagne was the embodiment of honor in both person and position. A conqueror, a philanthropist, lover of the arts and a highly devout Christian, Charlemagne stands as one of the important figures of the first millennium, and the forefather of Central Europe as it stands today.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_SIXTEENTH_NAME" >
			<Text>Ramkhamhaeng </Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREATPERSON_PLATI_SIXTEENTH_ACTIVE" >
			<Text>City with Government Plaza gains +15% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production if you are a Suzerain of a Militaristic City State. Gain 2 [ICON_Envoy] Envoys.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_PEDIA_GREATPEOPLE_PAGE_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_SIXTEENTH_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" >
			<Text>In 1278, a prince named "Ramkhamhaeng" inherited the small and unimportant kingdom of Sukhothai. In twenty years, employing a brilliant combination of military genius and shrewd diplomacy, he expanded his country's borders and influence to cover much of Southeast Asia. During his reign Ramkhamhaeng expanded his kingdom's dominance west into Burma, east into Laos, and south down the Malay Peninsula. The king was a shrewd diplomat as well as a warlord; many territories joined his confederation voluntarily. Ramkhamhaeng did not seek to dominate Southeast Asia, rather he promoted trade and diplomatic alliances with surrounding kingdoms. Most of what we know of Ramkhamhaeng's rule comes from a stone inscription he created in 1292 towards the end of his rule. This is the earliest surviving example of Thai language, and it portrays him as a wise and benevolent leader. Ramkhamhaeng is viewed today as a great leader and the first to rule over a united Siam (later Thailand). It should be remembered however that almost all that we know about him comes from the stone inscription that he himself created. If he did have any major flaws, would he have carved them into the living rock for all of history to see? (Would any of today's world leaders do so?) Still, there is plenty of independent evidence to show that he successfully created a great empire and his people prospered during his reign. And that's a record that any leader could be proud of.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_TWELWTH_NAME" >
			<Text>Maria Theresa </Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREATPERSON_PLATI_TWELWTH_ACTIVE" >
			<Text>Unique Improvements provided by City States give +2 [ICON_CULTURE] Adjacency bonus to Theatre Squares. Gain 2 [ICON_Envoy] Envoys.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_PEDIA_GREATPEOPLE_PAGE_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_TWELWTH_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" >
			<Text>During the 18th century, the Holy Roman Empire and the powerful Habsburg Monarchy of Austria were led by the ever-persistent Maria Theresa, who defied the European powers opposed to her reign and bravely served the subjects of her kingdom. In nearly 650 years of Habsburg rule, Maria Theresa was the first and only female to ever lead the empire, and she proved to be among the most successful rulers in their history. Maria Theresa is viewed today as a wise, contemplative leader, whose conservative policies and careful judgment improved the welfare of the Austrian people as well as those within the Habsburg dominion. Although she inherited the throne during a tumultuous period, with little personal experience in governing, she managed to secure her crown and assertively rule the Habsburg monarchy for 40 years.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_FIFTEENTH_NAME" >
			<Text>Haile Selassie</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREATPERSON_PLATI_FIFTEENTH_ACTIVE" >
			<Text>Grants +2 Diplomatic Victory points.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_PEDIA_GREATPEOPLE_PAGE_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_FIFTEENTH_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" >
			<Text>Known as the "Conquering Lion of the Tribe of Judah," "King of Kings," and "Elect of God," Haile Selassie ruled Ethiopia as emperor for nearly 40 years in the 20th century. Born as Lij Tafari Makonnen in 1892, the man who came to be known as Haile Selassie spent his life serving the interests of Ethiopia and bringing his nation to the forefront of African politics. Best known for reforming the ancient feudal practices of Ethiopia through his attempts at modernizing the nation, Haile Selassie worked tirelessly to gain international recognition for Ethiopia on the world stage. His legacy in global politics has been surpassed only by his role as the messiah of the Rastafari religion, among whose followers he is venerated as the god who will lead the Rastas back to their homeland of Ethiopia. In 1935, the Italian regime led by Benito Mussolini declared war on Ethiopia, invading in the fall. This conflict came to be known as the Second Italo-Abyssinian War (the first having occurred in the late 1800s). After brief fighting between the Italian and Ethiopian forces, including several battles led by Selassie himself, Italy succeeded in occupying and eventually annexing the African nation. With Italy's successful campaign against Ethiopia, Haile Selassie was forced into exile, but not before pleading the case for Ethiopia's defense at the League of Nations. Despite his galvanizing speech that railed against the Fascist movement of Italy, his plea fell on deaf ears, and Selassie was left to bide his time. He would spend the next five years residing in England, where he continued to speak out against the Italian occupation and attempted to garner support from the international community for a movement to reclaim his country. With the outbreak of World War II, in 1939, efforts were finally undertaken to liberate Ethiopia from the Italian regime, spearheaded by the British during the East African Campaign. Joined by selected units of the Ethiopian military, this liberation army came to be known as the Gideon Force and was instrumental in the fight to retake the Ethiopian homeland. By 1942, the Italians had surrendered and were forced to acknowledge the renewed sovereignty of Ethiopia, with Haile Selassie returning to the capital city of Addis Ababa. Having found little solidarity in the League of Nations, Selassie became a major proponent of the United Nations, with its increased provisions for international security, and secured Ethiopia's position as a founding member in 1948. Over the following years, Selassie continued his quest to modernize Ethiopia through reform while also improving his nation's foreign affairs and international recognition. In the 1960s Selassie led the Organization of African Unity, predecessor to the modern African Union. With the goal of creating solidarity between the independent states of the African continent, Selassie believed that a unified voice would strengthen the people of Africa. Although Selassie tried to establish the organization as more than just an ideological entity, the organization was left with little authority or actual power without the backing of a military force. While working with the international community, Selassie was also focused on improving the welfare of his people at home. Although his efforts to break the nobility's hold on land ownership were met with limited success, the initiative sparked a movement that carried on past his reign. Reforms were also made to provide greater access to educational facilities, while economic programs ensured a just system of taxation. Despite the goodwill generated by these domestic programs, Selassie's efforts to increase his own authority through modifications to the constitution resulted in an increasingly visible dissident movement. Late in the 1960s, Marxist ideologies took root in Ethiopia, and as the people suffered through a famine and drought in the early 1970s, Selassie's popularity dwindled. An economic crisis that led to soaring inflation would be the final straw, as Selassie tenuously maintained his position until 1974, when he was deposed and arrested by a Marxist military group known as The Derg. While living under house arrest, Haile Selassie died mysteriously in 1975, with conflicting reports as to the exact cause. While the official account from the military stated that he died as a result of illness, many still believe that he was assassinated by his captors. It wasn't until some 25 years later, in November of 2000, that Haile Selassie was finally given a proper funeral befitting his status. The Rastafarian Movement came about through the words of Jamaican activist Marcus Garvey, whose philosophical views created the foundations for the religion as it is known today. Garvey's words "Look to Africa for the crowning of a Black King, he shall be the Redeemer" were seen as a prophecy fulfilled by the coronation of Haile Selassie in 1930. Although Selassie was himself an Orthodox Christian, he never confirmed nor denied his position as the Rastafarian messiah, and he visited Jamaica in 1966 to be met by tens of thousands of Rastafarian believers. Haile Selassie is widely viewed today as both an eloquent statesman and a passionate leader who faced a number of difficulties during his reign, yet continually sought only to improve his people's welfare and his nation's stability. Selassie's views on international cooperation and diplomacy were influential not only in the future of Ethiopia, and Africa as a whole, but also throughout the international community.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_FOURTEENTH_NAME" >
			<Text>Ataturk</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREATPERSON_PLATI_FOURTEENTH_ACTIVE" >
			<Text>Grants 400 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production towards any Construction or Unit training. Three [ICON_Charges] Charges.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_PEDIA_GREATPEOPLE_PAGE_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_FOURTEENTH_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" >
			<Text>Mustafa Kemal Atatürk, or Mustafa Kemal Pasha until 1921, and Ghazi Mustafa Kemal from 1921 until 1934 was a Turkish field marshal, revolutionary statesman, author, and the founding father of the Republic of Turkey, serving as its first president from 1923 until his death in 1938. Atatürk came to prominence for his role in securing the Ottoman Turkish victory at the Battle of Gallipoli (1915) during World War I. Following the defeat and dissolution of the Ottoman Empire, he led the Turkish National Movement, which resisted mainland Turkey's partition among the victorious Allied powers. Establishing a provisional government in the present-day Turkish capital Ankara (known in English at the time as Angora), he defeated the forces sent by the Allies, thus emerging victorious from what was later referred to as the Turkish War of Independence. He subsequently proceeded to abolish the decrepit Ottoman Empire and proclaimed the foundation of the Turkish Republic in its place. As the president of the newly formed Turkish Republic, Atatürk initiated a rigorous program of political, economic, and cultural reforms with the ultimate aim of building a modern, progressive and secular nation-state. He made primary education free and compulsory, opening thousands of new schools all over the country. He also introduced the Latin-based Turkish alphabet, replacing the old Ottoman Turkish alphabet. Turkish women received equal civil and political rights during Atatürk's presidency. In particular, women were given voting rights in local elections by Act no. 1580 on 3 April 1930 and a few years later, in 1934, full universal suffrage. Ideologically a secularist and nationalist, his policies and socio-political theories became known as Kemalism. Due to his military and political accomplishments, Atatürk is regarded as one of the most important political leaders of the 20th century.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_THIRTEENTH_NAME" >
			<Text>Meiji</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREATPERSON_PLATI_THIRTEENTH_ACTIVE" >
			<Text>Grants [ICON_TechBoosted] Boost to all Industrial Era technologies.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_PEDIA_GREATPEOPLE_PAGE_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_THIRTEENTH_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" >
			<Text>Meiji, in full Meiji Tennō, personal name Mutsuhito, (1852 - 1912), emperor of Japan from 1867 to 1912, during whose reign Japan was dramatically transformed from a feudal country into one of the great powers of the modern world. At the time of Emperor Meiji's birth in 1852, Japan was a feudal pre-industrial country dominated by the isolationist Tokugawa shogunate and the daimyō subject to it, who ruled over the country's 270 decentralized domains. By the time of his death, Japan had undergone an extensive political, economic, and social revolution and emerged as one of the great powers on the world stage. The New York Times summarized this transformation at the emperor's funeral in 1912: "the contrast between that which preceded the funeral car and that which followed it was striking indeed. Before it went old Japan; after it came new Japan." The Japanese take pride in the Meiji Restoration, as it and the accompanying industrialization allowed Japan to become the preeminent power in the Pacific and a major player in the world within a generation. Yet, Emperor Meiji's role in the Restoration, as well as the amount of personal authority and influence he wielded during his reign, remains debatable. He kept no diary, wrote almost no letters (unlike his father) and left "no more than three or four" photographs.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_ELEVENTH_NAME" >
			<Text>Lee Kuan Yew</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREATPERSON_PLATI_ELEVENTH_ACTIVE" >
			<Text>[ICON_GreatMerchant] Great Merchants gain +1 [ICON_Charges] Charge.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_PEDIA_GREATPEOPLE_PAGE_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_ELEVENTH_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" >
			<Text>Lee Kuan Yew, born Harry Lee Kuan Yew, often referred to by his initials LKY, was a Singaporean barrister and statesman who served as the first prime minister of Singapore between 1959 and 1990, and the secretary-general of the People's Action Party between 1954 and 1992. Lee was born in Singapore during British colonial rule. After graduating from Raffles Institution, he won a scholarship to Raffles College (now the National University of Singapore). During the Japanese occupation, Lee escaped being the victim of a purge, before subsequently starting his own businesses while working as an administration service officer for the Japanese propaganda office. After World War II ended, Lee briefly attended the London School of Economics before transferring to Fitzwilliam College, Cambridge to study law, graduating in 1947. He was called to the Bar from the Middle Temple in 1950. Upon his return to Singapore, he practised as an advocate and solicitor whilst campaigning for the British to relinquish their colonial rule. Lee co-founded the People's Action Party (PAP) in 1954 and won his first seat at the Tanjong Pagar division during the 1955 general election. He became the de facto opposition leader in parliament, to Chief Ministers David Marshall and Lim Yew Hock of the Labour Front. Lee led his party to its first electoral victory in 1959 and was appointed as the state's first prime minister. To attain complete home rule from Britain, Lee campaigned for a merger with other former British territories in a national referendum to form Malaysia in 1963. Racial strife and ideological differences later led to Singapore's expulsion from Malaysia and subsequent independence in 1965, less than two years after the merger. With overwhelming parliamentary control at every general election, Lee oversaw Singapore's transformation into a developed country with a high-income economy within his premiership. In the process, he forged a highly effective, anti-corrupt government and civil service. Lee eschewed populist policies in favour of long-term social and economic planning, championing civic nationalism through meritocracy and multiracialism as governing principles, making English the lingua franca to integrate its immigrant society and to facilitate trade with the world, whilst mandating bilingualism in schools to preserve the students' mother tongue and ethnic identity. An advocate for Asian values and a proponent of pragmatism, Lee's premiership especially in the West was described as being semi-authoritarian and characterised as a sort of a hybrid regime or a guided democracy. Critics have accused him of curtailing press freedoms, imposing narrow limits on public protests, restricting labour movements from industrial or strike action through anti-union legislation and co-option, and bringing defamation lawsuits against prominent political opponents. However, others argue his actions as having been necessary for the country's early development, and that he was a benevolent dictator. During the three decades in which Lee held office, Singapore grew from a developing country to one of the most developed nations in Asia and the world.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_TENTH_NAME" >
			<Text>Akbar</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREATPERSON_PLATI_TENTH_ACTIVE" >
			<Text>One free Wild Card Policy slot in any Government.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_PEDIA_GREATPEOPLE_PAGE_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_TENTH_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" >
			<Text>Abu'l-Fath Jalal-ud-din Muhammad Akbar, popularly known as Akbar the Great, and also as Akbar I, was the third Mughal emperor, who reigned from 1556 to 1605. A strong personality and a successful general, Akbar gradually enlarged the Mughal Empire to include much of the Indian subcontinent. His power and influence, however, extended over the entire subcontinent because of Mughal military, political, cultural, and economic dominance. To unify the vast Mughal state, Akbar established a centralised system of administration throughout his empire and adopted a policy of conciliating conquered rulers through marriage and diplomacy. To preserve peace and order in a religiously and culturally diverse empire, he adopted policies that won him the support of his non-Muslim subjects. Eschewing tribal bonds and Islamic state identity, Akbar strove to unite far-flung lands of his realm through loyalty, expressed through an Indo-Persian culture, to himself as an emperor. Akbar's reign significantly influenced the course of Indian history. During his rule, the Mughal Empire tripled in size and wealth. He created a powerful military system and instituted effective political and social reforms. By abolishing the sectarian tax on non-Muslims and appointing them to high civil and military posts, he was the first Mughal ruler to win the trust and loyalty of the native subjects. He had Sanskrit literature translated, participated in native festivals, realising that a stable empire depended on the co-operation and good-will of his subjects. Thus, the foundations for a multicultural empire under Mughal rule were laid during his reign. Akbar was succeeded as emperor by his son, Prince Salim, later known as Jahangir. Akbar left a rich legacy both for the Mughal Empire as well as the Indian subcontinent in general. He firmly entrenched the authority of the Mughal Empire in India and beyond, after it had been threatened by the Afghans during his father's reign, establishing its military and diplomatic superiority. During his reign, the nature of the state changed to a secular and liberal one, with emphasis on cultural integration.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_NINTH_NAME" >
			<Text>Askia</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREATPERSON_PLATI_NINTH_ACTIVE" >
			<Text>Yields gained from pillaging are doubled for districts.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_PEDIA_GREATPEOPLE_PAGE_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_NINTH_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" >
			<Text>Moḥammad ibn Abī Bakr Ture, also known as Moḥammad I Askia (reigned 1493–1528), welded the central region of the western Niger into a single Songhai empire, the largest in African history. Although he fought several military campaigns, he is primarily remembered for reorganizing, modernizing and bringing stability to the Songhai. He is also remembered for making a famous pilgrimage to Mecca. Askia was a general under Sunni Ali, the first great leader of the Songhai Empire. Ali extended Songhai control along the Niger River, capturing the wealthy cities of Timbuktu and Jenne. Although nominally a Muslim, Ali continued to practice African animism as well, tolerating Muslim and non-Muslims within his kingdom. In 1492 Ali died in a freak accident; he and his horse fell in a river and were swept over a waterfall. Ali was succeeded by his son, Sunni Baru. Askia almost immediately began plotting Baru's overthrow, successfully gaining power in 1493 with the assistance of Muslim rebels. During his reign Askia expanded the empire to the north, south, and west, fighting successful campaigns against various neighboring cities and kingdoms. Not all of his battles were successful, however, and he is generally acknowledged to be an adequate but not exceptional military leader. Askia ruled for some thirty-five years. In 1528, old and blind, he was deposed by one of his sons, dying some 10 years later. He is judged to be an extremely competent administrator, his reign a golden age for religion and knowledge in Western Africa. While not a great general, he was able to expand his empire and to hold on to what he had taken until age robbed him of his powers. Overall, Askia is generally considered to be one of the best sub-Saharan rulers in history.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_EIGHTH_NAME" >
			<Text>Harun al-Rashid</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREATPERSON_PLATI_EIGHTH_ACTIVE" >
			<Text>[ICON_TradeRoute] Trade Routes provide +1 [ICON_SCIENCE] Science for every 6 tiles they travel if Civilization is in a [ICON_GLORY_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_PEDIA_GREATPEOPLE_PAGE_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_EIGHTH_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" >
			<Text>Harun al-Rashid (which translates roughly as "Aaron the Rightly Guided") was the fifth Abbasid Caliph, ruling the Arabian Empire from 786 to 809 AD. During his reign the Caliphate stretched from Spain in the west to Anatolia in the north to India in the east, and it was the largest and most powerful political entity in the world. Harun was an able ruler, and his reign was a time of scientific and cultural advancement and prosperity for his subjects. At the start of Harun's reign, the Caliphate's capital was in Baghdad, a new city founded by an earlier Caliph. The city was a center of arts, science and religion, with many beautiful buildings. There Harun founded the "House of Wisdom," a library and research facility which collected and translated scientific writings from Persian, Indian, Greek, and Roman texts. Under Harun Baghdad would blossom, becoming perhaps the largest and richest city in the world. Later Harun would move his government to the strategically important city of ar-Raqqah, but Baghdad would remain a great city of arts, science and commerce for centuries to come (the city would be conquered and sacked by the Mongols in 1258). A somewhat fantastic description of Harun may be found in "The Thousand and One Nights," in which the Caliph is described as living in a sumptuous palace flowing with gold, silver, and jewels. Although exaggerated, there is a strong element of truth to the tale. During Harun's reign huge amounts of wealth poured into the Empire, and a goodly portion of it made it to the Caliph's coffers. According to ancient historians, Harun's wife insisted that all utensils and plates at her table be made of gold and festooned with jewels. Politically, Harun attempted to maintain cordial relations with the European powers. He had direct diplomatic relations with Charlemagne, and in these pre-Crusade years Europeans had free access to Jerusalem and the Holy Lands. He also had diplomatic relations with the Imperial Court in China. However, his relations were somewhat less friendly with the Byzantines. Under his father, Harun had led an army through Turkey to the gates of Constantinople, capitol of the Byzantine Empire. After negotiation with the Empress Irene, Harun agreed to spare the city in return for an annual tribute of 70,000 gold coins. When Irene was deposed and the Byzantines reneged on the agreement in 806, Harun led another army north and once again forced the Byzantines to capitulate. Although there were wars and internal trouble, most of Rashid's reign was peaceful and prosperous. The Caliphate enjoyed economic and industrial growth, plus an explosion in trade. Harun was a lover of music and poetry, and he gave lavish gifts to artists in his court. Although not necessarily a great leader, Rashid did rule the Arabian Empire competently at the very height of its power and wealth.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_SOVEREIGN_FIRST_NAME" >
			<Text>Louis XIV</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREATPERSON_PLATI_SOVEREIGN_FIRST_ACTIVE" >
			<Text>Grants 3 Slots for [ICON_GreatWork_Landscape] Great Works of Art to all Government Plaza buildings. [ICON_GreatWork_Sculpture] Sculptures placed there have tripled [ICON_CULTURE] Culture output.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_PEDIA_GREATPEOPLE_PAGE_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_SOVEREIGN_FIRST_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" >
			<Text>Louis XIV, also known as Louis the Great or the Sun King, was King of France from 1643 until his death in 1715. His reign of 72 years and 110 days is the longest of any sovereign in history whose date is verifiable. During Louis's long reign, France emerged as the leading European power and regularly asserted its military strength. A conflict with Spain marked his entire childhood, while during his personal rule, the kingdom took part in three major continental conflicts, each against powerful foreign alliances: the Franco-Dutch War, the Nine Years' War, and the War of the Spanish Succession. In addition, France also contested shorter wars, such as the War of Devolution and the War of the Reunions. Warfare defined Louis's foreign policy and his personality shaped his approach. Impelled by "a mix of commerce, revenge, and pique", he sensed that war was the ideal way to enhance his glory. In peacetime, he concentrated on preparing for the next war. He taught his diplomats that their job was to create tactical and strategic advantages for the French military. Significant achievements during his reign which would go on to have a wide influence on the early modern period well into the Industrial Revolution and until today, include the construction of the Canal du Midi, the patronage of artists, and the founding of the French Academy of Sciences. The anti-Bourbon Napoleon described him not only as "a great king", but also as "the only King of France worthy of the name". Leibniz, the German Protestant philosopher, commended him as "one of the greatest kings that ever was". The historian and philosopher Voltaire wrote: "His name can never be pronounced without respect and without summoning the image of an eternally memorable age". Voltaire's history, The Age of Louis XIV, named Louis' reign as not only one of the four great ages in which reason and culture flourished, but the greatest ever.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_SOVEREIGN_ZAYED_NAME" >
			<Text>Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREATPERSON_PLATI_SOVEREIGN_ZAYED_ACTIVE" >
			<Text>Your cities receive +15% [ICON_GOLD] Gold for each different [ICON_Power] Power-providing Strategic Resource they have.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_PEDIA_GREATPEOPLE_PAGE_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_SOVEREIGN_ZAYED_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" >
			<Text>Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan was an Emirati politician, statesman, and philanthropist who served as the first president of the United Arab Emirates from 1971 until his death in 2004. He is credited as the founding father and the principal driving force behind the formation of the UAE, uniting seven emirates. He was considered a relatively liberal ruler, and permitted private media. However, they were expected to practice self-censorship and avoid criticism of Zayed or the ruling families. Freedom of worship was permitted, and to a certain extent allowances were made for expatriate cultures, but this did not always sit comfortably in the eyes of the wider Arab world with Zayed's role as a Muslim head of state. Sheikh Zayed was determined to unite the Emirates into federation. In a seminal meeting on 18 February 1968 at a desert highland on the border between Dubai and Abu Dhabi, Sheikh Zayed and Sheikh Rashid bin Saeed Al Maktoum of Dubai shook hands on the principle of founding a Federation and attempting to invite other trucial rulers to join in order that a viable nation be formed in the wake of the British withdrawal. In 1971, after occasionally difficult negotiations with the other six rulers of the Trucial States, the United Arab Emirates was formed. Zayed was appointed to the presidency of the UAE in 1971 and was reappointed on four more occasions: 1976, 1981, 1986, and 1991. In 1974, Zayed settled the outstanding border dispute with Saudi Arabia by the Treaty of Jeddah by which Saudi Arabia received the output of the Shaybah oilfield and access to the lower Persian Gulf in return for recognising the UAE. Zayed was one of the wealthiest men in the world. A Forbes estimate put his fortune at around US$20 billion in 2004. The source of this wealth was almost exclusively due to the immense oil wealth of Abu Dhabi and the Emirates, which sit on a pool of a tenth of the world's proven oil reserves.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_SOVEREIGN_FRIDRIK_GREAT_NAME" >
			<Text>Frederick the Great</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREATPERSON_PLATI_SOVEREIGN_FRIDRIK_GREAT_ACTIVE" >
			<Text>Gain [ICON_SCIENCE] Science equal to 25% of the [ICON_GOLD] Purchase cost of the Unit. All land combat units within 2 tiles regain all [ICON_Movement] Movement and Attack capability. 2 [ICON_Charges] Charges.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_PEDIA_GREATPEOPLE_PAGE_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_SOVEREIGN_FRIDRIK_GREAT_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" >
			<Text>Frederick II was King in Prussia from 1740 until 1772, and King of Prussia from 1772 until his death in 1786. His most significant accomplishments include his military successes in the Silesian wars, his reorganisation of the Prussian Army, the First Partition of Poland, and his patronage of the arts and the Enlightenment. Frederick was the last Hohenzollern monarch titled King in Prussia, declaring himself King of Prussia after annexing Royal Prussia from the Polish–Lithuanian Commonwealth in 1772. Prussia greatly increased its territories and became a major military power in Europe under his rule. He became known as Frederick the Great. Frederick was a supporter of enlightened absolutism, stating that the ruler should be the first servant of the state. He modernised the Prussian bureaucracy and civil service, and pursued religious policies throughout his realm that ranged from tolerance to segregation. He reformed the judicial system and made it possible for men of lower status to become judges and senior bureaucrats. Frederick also encouraged immigrants of various nationalities and faiths to come to Prussia, although he enacted oppressive measures against Catholics in Silesia and Polish Prussia. He supported the arts and philosophers he favoured, and allowed freedom of the press and literature. Frederick was almost certainly homosexual, and his sexuality has been the subject of much study. Because he died childless, he was succeeded by his nephew, Frederick William II. He is buried at his favourite residence, Sanssouci in Potsdam. Nearly all 19th-century German historians made Frederick into a romantic model of a glorified warrior, praising his leadership, administrative efficiency, devotion to duty and success in building Prussia into a great power in Europe. Frederick remained an admired historical figure through Germany's defeat in World War I, and the Nazis glorified him as a great German leader prefiguring Adolf Hitler, who personally idolised him. His reputation became less favourable in Germany after World War II, partly due to his status as a Nazi symbol. Regardless, historians in the 21st century tend to view Frederick as an outstanding military leader and capable monarch, whose commitment to enlightenment culture and administrative reform built the foundation that allowed the Kingdom of Prussia to contest the Austrian Habsburgs for leadership among the German states.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_SOVEREIGN_GEDIMINAS_NAME" >
			<Text>Gediminas</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREATPERSON_PLATI_SOVEREIGN_GEDIMINAS_ACTIVE" >
			<Text>Chosen city gains +5 Loyalty per turn. Three [ICON_Charges] Charges.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_PEDIA_GREATPEOPLE_PAGE_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_SOVEREIGN_GEDIMINAS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" >
			<Text>A man who established the biggest state in Europe of the time, streching from Baltic Sea to Black Sea and founder of a dynasty that would come to rule over Poland, Hungary and Bohemia - Gediminas - was the Grand Duke of Lithuania from 1316 until death. He is considered the founder of Lithuania's capital Vilnius. He was a founder of a new Lithuanian dynasty; the Gediminids, and laid the foundations of the state's expansion while sometimes referred as the "true" state founder. His sons and grandsons in remarkable two centuries of fierce warfare, managed to unify into a proper warrior state a country that was nothing more than a loose federation of tribes before, mount resistance against the aggression of the Catholic holy orders and conquer vast swathes of land in the East.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_RBORGIA_NAME" >
			<Text>Al-Hakam II</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREATPERSON_PLATI_RBORGIA_ACTIVE" >
			<Text>Every non-majority Religion provides +1 [ICON_Amenities] Amenity to your cities. This bonus is doubled in [ICON_GLORY_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Ages.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_PEDIA_GREATPEOPLE_PAGE_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_RBORGIA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" >
			<Text>Second Umayyad caliph of al-Andalus, son of the great Abd al-Rahman III, born in November 915 AD in the great city of Cordoba, died in that same great city in October 976, his great reign represented the greatest period in the caliphate; under his personal patronage, Moorish arts and science reached a golden age in al-Andalus. Al-Hakam II sought to improve his people’s lot, despite the Christians battering at the door. Already a rich kingdom, al-Hakam sponsored irrigation projects to boost agricultural output, widened streets in his towns, and ordered the building of more markets. He assembled a great personal library for use by scholars invited from across both Muslim and Christian lands, supposedly as large as 600 thousand books (more than one historian disputes this, many pegging the figure at a only 400 thousand). Construction projects included the expansion of the mosque in Cordoba and the completion of the royal residence Medina Azahara. The importance of Al-Andalus for today is that it shows us people with different religious affiliations can live together on the basis of humanitarian values (convivencia). There were Muslims, Jews, and Christians who lived together peacefully relative to any other place in the world at that time. The non-Muslims were free to live their religion as long as they are respectful to Muslims. Muslims were not allowed to consider or behave them as a second-class citizens.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_BISMARK_NAME" >
			<Text>Otto von Bismark</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREATPERSON_PLATI_BISMARK_ACTIVE" >
			<Text>Grants a free Diplomatic Policy slot in any Government.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_PEDIA_GREATPEOPLE_PAGE_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_BISMARK_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" >
			<Text>Otto, Prince of Bismarck, Count of Bismarck-Schönhausen, Duke of Lauenburg (1 April 1815 – 30 July 1898), born Otto Eduard Leopold von Bismarck, was a Prussian and later German statesman and diplomat. Bismark managed to orchestrate three wars, which he decisively won thanks to the crack German army. He even managed to make one of the nations he forced into war, Austria-Hungary, into a junior member of an alliance that Germany dominated! That’s not even mentioning that he was largely responsible for creating the German Empire, uniting it under the Prussian dominated North German Confederation and minor German states. He kept Europe at peace for a generation. With a whirling dervish approach to alliances and treaties, he managed to decisively check any outbreak of war between the major European powers, even though France was largely becoming resurgent and powerful. He even held two Congresses, both held in Berlin, to resolve European differences, the first one resolving the Bulgarian Crisis caused by the Russo-Turkish war of 1877–78 and the second one resolving European claims to Africa.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_ARBE_NAME" >
			<Text>Enrico Dandolo</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREATPERSON_PLATI_ARBE_ACTIVE" >
			<Text>Grants a free Diplomatic Policy slot in any Government.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_PEDIA_GREATPEOPLE_PAGE_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_ARBE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" >
			<Text>Enrico Dandolo is today considered one of the greatest Venetian Doges. He took control of a mercantile power in decline, riven by corruption and inefficiency, challenged by great and small powers across the region. Trade had declined, and its military was moribund. By his death, he had ended all outside threats to Venice's influence, and made it the dominant power in Mediterranean trade again. Historians have referred to Dandolo as the "founder of the Venetian colonial empire." Venice itself would be prosperous, stable and secure for the next century.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_KOSEMI_NAME" >
			<Text>Kösem Sultan</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREATPERSON_PLATI_KOSEMI_ACTIVE" >
			<Text>+1 Spy Capacity. Succesful spy operations grant you [ICON_Gold] Gold equal to 30% of [ICON_Gold] Income of a City where a Spy operation took place.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_PEDIA_GREATPEOPLE_PAGE_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_KOSEMI_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" >
			<Text>Kosem Sultan (c. 1589 – 2 September 1651) also known as Mahpeyker Sultan – was one of the most powerful women in Ottoman history. Kösem Sultan achieved power and influenced the politics of the Ottoman Empire when she became haseki sultan as favourite consort of Ottoman Sultan Ahmed I (r. 1603–1617) and valide sultan as mother of Murad IV (r. 1623–1640) and Ibrahim (r. 1640–1648), and grandmother of Mehmed IV (r. 1648–1687). Kösem lived in the Ottoman Empire as a courtier during the reign of six sultans: Ahmed I, Mustafa I, Osman II, Murad IV, Ibrahim, and Mehmed IV. After her death, she was known by the names "Valide-i Muazzama" (magnificent mother), "Vālide-i Maḳtūle" (murdered mother), and "Vālide-i Şehīde" (martyred mother). Venetian ambassador Simon Contarini mentions Kösem in his report in 1612 and portrays her as: "[A woman] of beauty and shrewdness, and furthermore ... of many talents, she sings excellently, whence she continues to be extremely well loved by the king ... Not that she is respected by all, but she is listened to in some matters and is the favorite of the king, who wants her beside him continually." Kösem's influence over the Sultan increased in the following years and it is said that she acted as one of his advisers. However, she refrained from involving herself constantly in serious issues as the Sultan refused to be overshadowed by his wife. Kösem is sometimes accused of trying to save her own position and influence throughout her long career "rather than that of the sultan or of the dynasty". It was Mehmed IV's mother, Turhan, who proved to be Kösem's true nemesis. When she was about 12 years old, Turhan was sent to the Topkapı Palace as a gift from the khan of Crimea to Kösem Sultan. It was probably Kösem Sultan who gave Turhan to Ibrahim as a concubine. Turhan turned out to be too ambitious a woman to lose such a high position without a fight. In her struggle to become valide sultan, Turhan was supported by the chief black eunuch in her household and the grand vizier, while Kösem was supported by the Janissary Corps. Although Kösem's position as valide was seen as the best for the government, the people resented the influence of the Janissaries on the government. In this power struggle, Kösem planned to dethrone Mehmed and replace him with another young grandson. According to one historian, this switching had more to do with replacing an ambitious daughter-in-law with one who was more easily controlled. The plan was unsuccessful as it was reported to Turhan by Meleki Hatun, one of Kösem's slaves, that Kösem was said to be plotting Mehmed's removal and replacement by another grandson with a more pliant mother. Whether Turhan sanctioned it or not, Kösem Sultan was murdered three years after becoming regent for her young grandson. It is rumoured that Turhan ordered Kösem's assassination. Furthermore, some have speculated that Kösem was strangled with a curtain by the chief black eunuch of the harem, Tall Suleiman. The Ottoman renegade Bobovi, relying on an informant in the harem, states that Kösem was strangled with her own hair.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_BEG_NAME" >
			<Text>Ulug Beg</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GOODYHUT_LARGE_SCIENCE_DESCRIPTION" >
			<Text>[ICON_Science] [ICON_Science] [ICON_Science]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREATPERSON_PLATI_BEG_ACTIVE" >
			<Text>Recieve +200 [ICON_Science] Science every time you place a new Campus district.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_PEDIA_GREATPEOPLE_PAGE_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_BEG_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" >
			<Text>Ulugh Beg (22 March 1394 – 27 October 1449), was a Timurid sultan, as well as an astronomer and mathematician. Ulugh Beg was notable for his work in astronomy-related mathematics, such as trigonometry and spherical geometry, as well as his general interests in the arts and intellectual activities. It is thought that he spoke five languages: Arabic, Persian, Turkic, Mongolian, and a small amount of Chinese. During his rule (first as a governor, then outright) the Timurid Empire achieved the cultural peak of the Timurid Renaissance through his attention and patronage. Samarkand was captured and given to Ulugh Beg by his father Shah Rukh. He built the great Ulugh Beg Observatory in Samarkand between 1424 and 1429. It was considered by scholars to have been one of the finest observatories in the Islamic world at the time and the largest in Central Asia. Ulugh Beg was subsequently recognized as the most important observational astronomer from the 15th century by many scholars. He also built the Ulugh Beg Madrasah (1417–1420) in Samarkand and Bukhara, transforming the cities into cultural centers of learning in Central Asia. His beliefs are summarized by the words he left carved on walls of his Observatory: 'Religions rise and fall, empires crumble into dust, but the works of science are for all time'. However, Ulugh Beg's scientific expertise was not matched by his skills in governance. During his short reign, he failed to establish his power and authority. As a result, other rulers, including his family, took advantage of his lack of control, and he was subsequently overthrown and assassinated.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_AKBAR_NAME" >
			<Text>Julius II</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_GREATPERSON_PLATI_AKBAR_ACTIVE" >
			<Text>Grants 455 [ICON_Production] Production towards Wonder construction.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row tag="LOC_PEDIA_GREATPEOPLE_PAGE_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_PLATI_AKBAR_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" >
			<Text>Born Giuliano della Rovere (5 December 1443 – 21 February 1513), Pope Julius II was head of the Catholic Church and ruler of the Papal States from 1503 to his death in February 1513. Nicknamed the Warrior Pope or the Fearsome Pope, he chose his papal name not in honour of Pope Julius I but in emulation of Julius Caesar. One of the most powerful and influential popes, Julius II was a central figure of the High Renaissance and left a significant cultural and political legacy. As a result of his policies during the Italian Wars, the Papal States increased its power and centralization, and the office of the papacy continued to be crucial, diplomatically and politically, during the entirety of the 16th century in Italy and Europe. In 1506, Julius II established the Vatican Museums and initiated the rebuilding of the St. Peter's Basilica. The same year he organized the famous Swiss Guard for his personal protection and commanded a successful campaign in Romagna against local lords. The interests of Julius II lay also in the New World, as he ratified the Treaty of Tordesillas, establishing the first bishoprics in the Americas and beginning the Catholicization of Latin America. In 1508, he commissioned the Raphael Rooms and Michelangelo's paintings in the Sistine Chapel. Julius II was described by Machiavelli in his works as an ideal prince. Pope Julius II allowed people seeking indulgences to donate money to the Church, which would be used for the construction of Saint Peter's Basilica. He was fiercely satirized after his death by Erasmus of Rotterdam in Julius Excluded from Heaven, in which the drunken pope, denied entry by St Peter, justifies his worldly life and threatens to found his own paradise.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- POLICIES -->
		<Row Tag="LOC_POLICY_SOVEREIGNS_NAME" >
			<Text>Meritocracy</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_POLICY_SOVEREIGNS_DESCRIPTION" >
			<Text>+2 [ICON_GreatSovereigns] Great Sovereign points per turn.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_GOVERNMENTS_PAGE_POLICY_SOVEREIGNS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" >
			<Text>Plato, among others, advocated meritocracy as the most sensible form of public administration … in his case that rulers should be philosopher-kings whose right to rule came from their intellect and insight. Simply put, a meritocracy is a system in which the most talented and worthy gain advancement in the government bureaucracy, rather than, say, those who are close personal friends of the current ruler (or congressman), or those from a certain tribe or caste or religion. Most civilizations swing back and forth between some form of meritocracy and some less sensible method of choosing those who run things. This pattern repeats itself until the sun explodes and all life is wiped off of the face of the planet.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_POLICY_DIPLO_SOVER_POINTS_NAME" >
			<Text>International Nobility</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_POLICY_DIPLO_SOVER_POINTS_DESCRIPTION" >
			<Text>+1 [ICON_GreatSovereigns] Great Sovereign point per turn for every Diplomatic Quarter building.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_GOVERNMENTS_PAGE_POLICY_DIPLO_SOVER_POINTS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" >
			<Text>International relations are a tricky business. Merchant class who were used to dealing with foreigners often played the role of diplomats and ambassadors. As aristocratic dynasties transcended borders, so did the importance of international nobility - the kindred ties that influential families have established through the years (the nightmarish map of Holy Roman Empire riddled with border gore and over-frequent enclaves demonstrates this). Often these ties were taken advantage of to help state's cause diplomatically or militarily. At the same time, countries engaged in 'aristocratic diplomacy' often flung into Succession Wars and even lost their independence through Personal Unions.</Text>
		</Row>
</GameData>
